Jessica Perry

Jessica.jperry@outlook.com • San Francisco/Bay Area, CA • Github: JperryDev9 • Linkedin: jperry09

JOURNEY

I have worked in the Culinary industry for 15 years. Wanted to make a more considerable impact in my career so I decided to pivot my focus to technology. Self-taught front-end developer with aspirations to become a full-stack developer. Neurodivergent who loves dogs, good food, and adventures. I enjoy getting lost in the woods and meeting interesting people.

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Python | Git & Github | JavaScript | Unit Testing w/ Mocha | SCRUM

PROJECTS

Amazing Eggs, Eggs lovers landing page □

Oct 2021

Built an informational landing page about eggs designed for younger age groups; used HTML, CSS, and lavaScript.

AWARDS

Women Who Code + LINUX Foundation scholarship

Apr 07, 2022

Linux Foundation Training & Certification partnering with Women Who Code (WWCode), Cloud Foundry for Developers Certification Completion: 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GenerationUSA Jr. Web Development Program

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022 | Remote

- Built a mock restaurant menu website effectively using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Agile methodologies.
- Orchestrated Github monitoring and alerting for pull requests.
- Spent 250+ hours independently learning new technical skills adding to the program's curriculum of technical and professional skills.
- Cultivated a study group forum to assist cohort learners outside of class, providing additional resources and support.

Accounts Receivable Admin., JAM Services Inc.

2019 - 2020 | Livermore , CA

- Hired as Temporary Receptionist then promoted to Full-time employee in **three months** due to exceptional work ethic, accelerated learning ability, and exceptional customer service.
- Processed 1.2 million in combined credit, electronic, cash, and check payments per day, equivalent to 100 to 200 invoices across 25 to 30 unique customer accounts.
- Mentored and trained full-time regular and contract employees on the A/R process and procedure.

Chef, Culinary Professional

2006 - 2015

- Maintained and delegated various kitchen stations setting the standard for restaurant flow.
- Masterfully executed duties in a variety of roles from high-volume catering events to personal private nutritional planning.
- Executed multiple events of upwards of **200+ patrons** successfully thru collaboration, strong attention to detail, and strong verbal communication.

EDUCATION

Front-end Web Development Track, Treehouse.com

2021 - present

learning the fundamentals of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Workshops geared toward React and Python tracks.

Google IT Support Professional Course, Coursera.org

2020 - present

Intro to Coding, Shecodes Workshop □

2021

Culinary Arts, Associate's Degree,

2006 - 2008

California Culinary Academy , Le Cordon Bleu, San Francisco